Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
Records of the Institute of African American Affairs
1965-2018
New York University Archives
RG.9.8
96.17 Linear Feet in 90 record cartons, 12 manuscript boxes, and 1 flat box.
54 film reels
161 3.5" floppy disks
47 electronic discs (cd-rom)
2 dvd-r disks
175 videocassettes (digital betacam)
319 videocassettes (vhs)
282 audiocassettes
54 videocassettes (minidv)
4 videocassettes (dvcam)
22 sound discs (cd)
1 videocassettes (u-matic)
Correspondence.; Administrative records.; American literature -- African American authors.; African American theater; African American athletes; Clippings (information artifacts); African Americans |x Mental health; American literature |x Puerto Rican authors; Audiovisual materials.; African Americans -- Economic conditions.; Puerto Rican families -- New York (State) -- New York.; African Americans -- Politics and government.; African American art.; Reports.; African American college students.; Audiocassettes.; Pamphlets.; Lectures.; VHS; Press releases.
- Series I: Events Files
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: "The Black Church in the 80's" Rev. Herbert Daughtry, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 31142042260185
  - Emerging African Nations, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226018 5
  - MLK Memorial Concert, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Benin Catalog Orders/Sales, Exhibition Date 1981 - Present (Receipts of Payment) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Benin Exhibition "Images of Power" Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Benin Exhibition Listings, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Benin Exhibition Publicity, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Benin Exhibition "Images of Power" Publicity, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Black Scholars Lecture Series: "The Labor Union Movement - It's Importance in Developing Countries"/ Lillian Roberts, Speaker., 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Honorable Robert Davis, Comm. Lecture. Series, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Black Scholar Lecture Series: "Housing Trends in the Black Community: What Will the 80's Bring", 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Black History Reception, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Black History Month Reception, Feb 4, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Community Lecture Series: Rev. Daughtry, Feb 23, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Community Lecture Series: Dr. Albert Oliver, Mar 16, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cinema Series "Common Denominators" -, Mar 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Correspondence - Speakers., Mar 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Correspondence - Forms, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Correspondence - Personalized, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Forms, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Program Operation, Logistics, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Public Correspondence - Info. Requests, Comments, Etc., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Black Male Conference Part I: Publicity, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Registrants Forms/Responses, & Questionnaire Responses, Part I: Black Male Conference, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. I: Speakers' Papers/Correspondence., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. I: Topic Information, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. I: Programming, Logistics, Logistics-Operation, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Wyatt T. Walker, Apr 12, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Martin Luther King Salute: Canaan Baptist Church, Apr 12, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Black Theatre Forum - Correspondence to Speakers/Participants, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Black Theatre Forum Conference Expenditures, Revenues, & Pre-registration, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Black Theatre Forum Conference Forms, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Black Theatre Forum Conference Forms, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Black Theatre Forum Conference Funding: Proposals & Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Correspondence/Form Letters to Lecturers/Speakers., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Advance Registration Forms/Responses, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226019 3
  - Black Male Conference Correspondence-Personalized Pt. II:, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Forms, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. 2 Lecturer/Speaker. Responses, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Lecturer/Speaker. Responses, Correspondence, Papers, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Papers of Speakers, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Pgm. Operation/Logistics & Publicity, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Public Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Questionnaires to Public Responses, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Registrants Forms/Responses, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Speakers Info., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Black Male Conference Pt. II: Workshop(s) Info., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: Exhibition Budget & Expenses, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: External Correspondence concerning Exhibition, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: Patents and Pictures of Exhibition, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: Chronological Files, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: External Correspondence regarding exhibition, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Making America Work Exhibition: University Correspondence regarding exhibition, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Making America Work Exhibition, Feb 3, 1983-Feb 18, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Blacks in the West; W.L. Katz, Prof., Feb 4, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Black History Month Reception: A Salute to Paul Robeson, Feb 7, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Black History Month Reception: Paul Robeson Tribute, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226020 1
  - Dennis Rahim Watson, Ben Snow - Bobst, Feb 16, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Community Lecture Series: E. Graves, Feb 23, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference, Program Operation: Logistics, Budget, Programming, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference: Publicity, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Black Theatre Forum: 'A Total Perspective" Questionnaires, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference: Related Literature/Topics, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference, Speakers: Papers, Corres., Bio-Info., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference: Speaker/Possible Participants Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Black Theatre Forum-Conference: Speakers-Speeches, Lectures, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Association of Black Women in Higher Education, Inc. 4th Annual Conference, May 7, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Caribbean Conference Correspondence (Speaker(s) Solicitation), Letters., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Caribbean Conf. Forms, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Caribbean Conf. Letrs. of Responses & Returned Forms (Call for Papers), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Caribbean Conf. "Caribbean Culture & Politics: Today's Realities-Tomorrow's Directions," -- Program Operation (i.e. schedules, expenses), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Caribbean Conference: "Caribbean Culture & Politics: Today's Realities-Tomorrow's Directions," Publicity, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Caribbean Conference: Related info, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Series V. Community Lecture Series: Dr. Ben -Jochannon, May 17, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Community Lecture Series: Alice Childress, Oct 19, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Black Theater Forum: Correspondence-Earl Davis, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Black Theater Forum Conference: IAAA Correspondence (1), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Theater Mailing List, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Black Theater Forum Conference: IAAA Correspondence (2), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Association of Black Faculty & Students, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Black History Reception, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Community Lecture Series II: Robinson, Randall, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Catti James, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cinema Presentations, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Community Lecture Series III: Cross, Dr. Delores (1), 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Twelfth Annual Dr. Martin L. King Jr., Memorial Concert, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Lecture "The IAAA at NYU" Spkr.: Earl Davis, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Program Schedules & Operations, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Minority Student/Faculty Reception 10/10/84, Oct 10, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Tom Sanders: Community Lecture Series I - Black Athletes Responsibility to the Black Community, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Cal Ramsay: Community Lecture Series I "The Black Athletes' Responsibility to the Black Community", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Paula Giddings 11/19/84, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Paula Giddings: Community Lecture Series II: "When and Where I Enter", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Black History Reception '85 "Diggers, Panama Canal: Creation of a Nation", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Making America Work: Black Contributions To American Business And Industry; Exhibition Paper by L. Bray; Pictures; Flyers, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - News Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Community Lecture Series III: Cross, Dr. Delores (2), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226021 9
  - Community Lecture Series V: Dr. Carlos Moore, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Carlos Moore, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Advertising & Press Releases, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budget & Program Planning, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Conference Flyers & Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Black History Month Reception: "Diggers, Panama Canal: Creation of a Nation" Ben Snow, Bobst Library, Feb 4, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Black History Calendar Reception - Bobst Library, Feb 4, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Judge Bruce Wright Lecture Series, Feb 13, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Catti James -Lecture Workshop "Celebration: Experiences in Black Art", Feb 13, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Essence - Susan Taylor "An Agenda For the Future Economic Empowerment and Love" (1), Mar 18, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Susan Taylor "An Agenda For the Future Economic Empowerment and Love" (2), Mar 18, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Association Black Counselors; The National Organizational Conference, Apr 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The National Association of Black Counselors --- The Nat'l Organizational Conference, Mar 31, 1985-Apr 5, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Afro-Brazilian Territory, Apr 24, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Association of Black Women in Higher Education, Inc. 7th Annual Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Paule Marshall - Community Lecture Series, Oct 16, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Michael Crowder, Oct 24, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Black Film Festival, Oct 28, 1985-Oct 30, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Women's Conference in Nairobi, Kenya, Oct 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226022 7
  - Community Symposium: Free Enterprise versus Military Rule in Third World Countries, Oct 25, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - A Special Tribute in celebration of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Ben Snow Lounge, Jan 15, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - [Living the Dream], 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lecture: "Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.: An African Perception." by Dr. John Kerefa-Smart, Feb 3, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Invisible America: "The Next Generation", Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photography Exhibition, Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence/Photographers, Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photo Exhibit-Correspondence (Program Operation, Forms, Etc), Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photo Exhibit-Correspondence (Unselected Photographers), Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photo Exhibition Programming: Planning, Operations, Budget & Logistical Set Up, Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Program Funding, Solicitation of Sponsorship, Photo Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Photographer Listings, Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Photo Exhibit - Photographers' Prints/Entered in Exhibition (1), Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Photo Exhibition Publicity, Press Releases, Commentaries, Etc., Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Photography Exhibition, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Photography Exhibition, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Photography Exhibit - Photographers' Prints/Entered in Exhibition (2), 2/7/86, Feb 7, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Photography Exhibition (2), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - David Dinkins, Feb 10, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Health Issues in the Black Community: Prognosis for Change, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Black History Month Film Festival, Feb 24, 1986-Feb 27, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226023 5
  - African Film Festival, Feb 24, 1986-Feb 27, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Malcolm X -The Master Teacher", Mar 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Community Lecture Series - "Women of the Royal Court of Benin"., Mar 20, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Angelina Pollack-Eltz, Afro-American Folk Medicine, Apr 2, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Poetry Reading: Fred Ramey, Betty Lawrence Bailey, May 12, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - South Africa: A Nation in Crisis, Sep 22, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - IAAA's First Annual Fundraising Cabaret Dinner Dance at CJ's Seafood Restaurant, Oct 12, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Minority Students Fall Orientation, Fall 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Simpson/Rodino Bill: Impact on Minority Communities, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "The Civil Rights Struggle Continued - 25 Years Later": Reception-Dr. Martin L. King, Jr., Jan 15, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Community Lecture Series: "Gov't & Politics in NYC-Implications for the Minority Community", Jan 27, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Black Filmmakers Mini-Film Festival 87: "Your Children Come Back to You," Alile Larkin; "Grey Area," Monona IAAA Reception, Theme: "Continent to Continent: A Ritual Experience", Feb 12, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Reception, Theme: Continent to Continent: A Ritual Experience", Feb 12, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "The Role of the Police Officer in the Minority Community" event cancelled, 2/12/87, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - "A Tribute to Civil Rights Leaders, Lest We Forget", Feb 25, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Annual ABFA Student/Faculty Basketball Game, Feb 27, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - GPA Marnold Fellow Program; Speakers: Earl S. Davis, Hon. Charles B. Rangel & Dean Alan Altshuler, GPA, Apr 6, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "Perceptions of Visual Structure as an Attitude of Non-Objective Art: Tools for the Layman to Evaluate Art," Dr. Adrienne W. Hoard, Guest Speaker, Apr 30, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Blind Beggar Press: 6th Annual Book Celebration, May 7, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Black Faculty/Administrator/Student Orientation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "Mandela" - Movie/video, Nov 9, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Ted Joans - Poet, "One of the last Black Bohemian-Beat Generation Poets", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Blacks and the Constitution (symposium), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Kwanza, Dec 7, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - "Kwanza Celebration", Dec 7, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Reception, Jan 19, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Recovering the Lost Treasures of Africa: A Lecture by Dr. Ekpo Eyo, Feb 4, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - A Tribute to James Baldwin, Feb 29, 1988-Mar 1, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "Afro-Americans & the Evolution of a Living Constitution" Teleconference, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Malumbo Ntshilontshilo, Speaking engagement "Stop the Executions of the South African Youth Tour," Cosponsored by IAAA & Young Socialist Alliance Student Organization at NYU, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226024 3
  - "Caribbean Empowerment in the 21st Century and Beyond", Jun 11, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "The Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution: Reflections on the Black Experience,", 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Black History Month Telecast, Feb 1, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Black Authors at NYU - Speaking on Their Works, 2/23/89, Oct 11, 1989-Aug 18, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Black Indians: A Hidden Heritage; Lecture by Prof. William L. Katz, Mar 29, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lecture-Chinua Achebe, Apr 13, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Faculty Roundtable Series, Women's Movement, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Prospect for Civilian Democracy in Nigeria, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Youth Revolts and the Prospects of Revolution in South Africa, by Dr. Baruch Hirson, Glascow University, Nov 14, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Swahili Lecture/Performance of Song and Poetry, Nov 16, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ethnic Diversity and Racial Consciousness in Brazil, Zumbi Conference, Nov 20, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Professor Claudine Brown - Gallatin Division, "Social Responsibilities In Museum Planning", Dec 12, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "The Restoration of African History - The Role of Egypt," by Dr. Yosef B. Hochannan, Feb 5, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "The Americana Paper Trail: The Untold African American Legacy," Dwayne D. Key, Speaker, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - African Heritage Month, Feb. 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "African Roots in Latino Culture," by Marta Moreno Vega, Feb 6, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Blacks in Science," by Dr. Ivan Van Sertima, Feb 8, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Castro, the Blacks, and Africa," by Dr. Carlos Moore, Feb 12, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Dr. Carlos, Ben Snow, Feb 12, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "African American Heroes in American Culture," Performed by Rod Rogers Dance Company, Feb 15, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, Feb 15, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Miles" A Biography of Miles Davis: Discussion by Quincy Troupe, an Author, Feb 21, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Quincy Troupe, Feb 21, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NYU Faculty Colloquium on Orality, Writing, and Culture, Feb 21, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "The African-American Scholar: Choosing a Life of Learning", Feb 22, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Mother, Sister, Chile," choreopoem by AWAMU, Mar 21, 1990-Mar 24, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "The Intersection of Race, Gender, and Class in the Health Professions", Mar 29, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - African American Graduate Students Public Policy Symposium, Robert F. Wagner Grad. Schl. of Public Svc.-NYU, Apr 5, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Black Church in America", May 3, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kofi Anyidoho: Poetry Reading, Nov 9, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Revelation's Exhibition: Francine Fels, Feb 1, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "The Role of the N.Y.C. Police Dept. in Minority Communities," Black History Month Reception & Lecture, Feb 5, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Clark Terry Quartet-Jazz Pg., Feb 19, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "Breaking the Chains: African American Slave Resistance," A Book Presentation/Lecture/Reception/Loren Katz-Spkr., Feb 19, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Women's History Month: Hazel Carby-Lecturer, Mar 7, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "300 Years Plus of African American Artifacts & Folk Art," A 2 Day African American Exhibition: Duane Keyes-Dalcour Art Enterprise, Mar 8, 1991-Mar 9, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - "Race, Gender and Representation," Lecture by Bell Hooks, Mar 26, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Film Screening & Reception: "Keep on Moving," by AWAMU, Apr 6, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Black Alumni Association, [EMPTY], Apr 6, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Blacks in the Media, Apr 11, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226025 0
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference, Correspondence (1), Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference; Correspondence (2), [EMPTY], Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power; Forms, Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference Programming, Planning, Etc., Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference Publicity, Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Kongo Carolina, Kongo New Orleans: Notes on a Major Transatlantic Art Tradition," Lecturer - Robert F. Thompson, Apr 16, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Minority Journalist Society Lecture-Guest Speaker Gil Noble, Apr 30, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - African American & Latino Awards Ceremony, May 1, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Great Zimbabwe Cross-cultural Reception: "The Best of Zimbabwe Display", May 19, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [Untitled folder containing material on Francine Fels' exhibit "Happy Birthday, Rev!"], May 28, 1991-Jul 2, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Francine Fels, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Happy Birthday, Rev!" Tribute to Alvin Ailey, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Series II: Association for Education in Journalism (AEJ)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226025 1
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - AEJ Correspondence, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hamilton, William P., Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hearn, Sandra, Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Mangual, Anna, Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Morris, Burnice Mr., Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Newton, Linda L., Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Reddix, Brenda R., Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - West, Charles, Intern, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226026 8
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Program Operations - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - AEJ Tapes, 73 [envelope]; Tapes of A.E.J. "Journalism & Minorities" Seminar, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Burrell, Judy, Intern, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chunn, Kelley, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Clark, Anthony J., undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - De Graffenreidt, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dorothy Langhorne, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Montemayor, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Walters, Barbara, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)